Revenge just rode into town
Red Hill is a action, thriller, western film directed by Patrick Hughes.
Young police officer Shane Cooper's first day on duty, after relocating to
the small town of Red Hill, rapidly turns into a nightmare.
News of a prison break, involving convicted murderer Jimmy Conway, sends the local law enforcement officers - led by
the town's ruling presence, Old Bill - into a panic and leads to a terrifying and bloody confrontation.
Shane Cooper, played by Ryan Kwanten.
Old Bill, played by Steve Bisley.
Jimmy Conway, played by Tom E. Lewis.
Alice Cooper, played by Claire van der Boom.
Slim, played by Christopher Davis.
Jim Barlow, played by Kevin Harrington.
Red Hill is a 2010 Australian neo-western thriller film written and
directed by Patrick Hughes in his directorial debut.
The film stars Ryan Kwanten, Steve Bisley, and Tom E.
The film explores themes of australia, small town, suicide, fire, rape.
The tone is intense.